{"data":[{"question":"The equipment in the office was badly in need of to be repaired.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"equipment","b":"in the office","c":"was badly","d":"to be repaired","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- To be repaired-> being repaired","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"A liter is one of the metric measurements, aren't they?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"one of the","c":"measurements","d":"aren't they","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Aren't they-> isn't it","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We thought he is planning to go on vacation after the first of the month.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"to go on vacation","c":"after","d":"the first of","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Is-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"There are a large amount of furniture in the storeroom to the left of the library entrance.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"of furniture","c":"in the storeroom","d":"to the left of","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The president refuses to accept either of the four new proposals made by the contractors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to accept","b":"either","c":"new proposals","d":"made by","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Either-> none","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"While searching for the wreckage of a unidentified aircraft, the Coast Guard encountered severe squalls at sea.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While searching","b":"the","c":"a","d":"severe squalls at sea","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Montaigne, the illustrious French philosophy, was elected mayor of Bordeaux, which was his home town.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was guarding","b":"treasures in","c":"would try to","d":"steal","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Was guarding-> were guarding\nThe expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The sun is a huge fiery globe at a average distance of 93,000,000 miles from the Earth.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"so difficult for","b":"to negotiate","c":"in their native language","d":"universal","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Universal-> universally","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"When I last saw Janet, she hurried to her next class on the other side of the campus and did not have time to talk.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"enabling","b":"to convey","c":"to incorporate","d":"were read","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- To incorporate: by incorporating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Because the residents had worked so diligent to renovate the old building, the manager had a party.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"the most common form","b":"existence","c":"others systems","d":"to express","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Others system-> other systems","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}